Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. London Office. Stationery Guard Books, 1952-1981 RL.11027
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. London Office. Stationery Guard Books
1952-1981
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. London Office
John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
RL.11027
4753
9 Linear Feet
Founded in New York, N.Y., in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the world's oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies. The London Office first opened in 1899 and reopened in 1926, and was JWT's first international office as well as the first international office of any American advertising agency. Collection consists of binders of standard stationery forms authorized for use by JWT officials, departments and subsidiaries. It includes letterhead, business cards, access permits, work flow and process forms, booklet covers and other paper items. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.Cataloged from inventory.
Collection Overview
Collection consists of binders of standard stationery forms authorized for use by JWT officials, departments and subsidiaries. It includes letterhead, business cards, access permits, work flow and process forms, booklet covers and other paper items. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.Cataloged from inventory.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Arrangement
Organized chronologically.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. London Office. Stationery Guard Books were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2008
Advertising agencies -- Great Britain; Advertising agencies -- Great Britain -- History; Advertising -- Great Britain; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
- Guard book, 1952-1981; 873880 (Box 1)
- Guard book, 1960-1966; 873881 (Box 2)
- Guard book, 1960-1966; 873882 (Box 3)
- Guard book, 1966-1973; 873883 (Box 4)
- Guard book, 1966-1973; 873943 (Box 5)
- Guard book, circa 1967; 873884 (Box 6)
- Guard book, circa 1975; 873885 (Box 7)
- Guard book, 1978-1981; 873886 (Box 8)
- Guard book, 1978-1981; 873887 (Box 9)
- Guard book, approximately 1970-1972 (Box 10)